Hello everyone welcome to Acer Life Ianb I am
Sumit Rajput today I am telling you the process of
how to download ICICI's land insurance policy,
so we will open the form, we will
search in G, we have to
open the first side, so
this is the home page of ICCI land board which has
opened, then we will go to support,
contact it,
see here, we will scroll down a bit,
here you can download the details policy by clicking on the service menu from the Oil Tech Care app
in your mobile
and also
see below, here you will see the required policy
copy, download policy copy details,
so see, I will show you by clicking on the required policy copy,
here you have to
go to the product code, select the motor here,
after that a little below you have to press the
next button, see enter
policy details here, you have to enter the policy number,
okay and here in two numbers you have to type the
engine chase, whatever you want, vehicle
registration number, here you will
type the vehicle registration number, fill your capture on this
and proceed,
after proceeding your policy will be generated,
so download policy details here
You can download the policy by going to enter your policy again and filling in the policy number directly. The
policy is fine. Similarly, you
can download the policy in IC Lord. Thank
you for watching.